- Photographs (Box-folder 1: 6-11)
  - Personal (Box-folder 1: 6-7)
    - Prince School class, photographic print, 1914 (Box-folder FB-21: 1)
    - Teenage performances, undated., 5 items. (Box-folder 1: 6)
    - Portraits, undated., 3 items. (Box-folder 1: 7)
  - Performances by students (Box-folder 1: 8-10)
    - Piggilly wiggily, ca. 1942 (Box-folder 1: 8)
    - Top hat, ca. 1942 (Box-folder 1: 8)
    - Unidentified, undated., 15 items. (Box-folder 1: 8-10)
  - Other individuals (Box-folder 1: 11)
    - Hall, Tom, 1930 (Box-folder 1: 11)
    - Purcell, Barbara, ca. 1942 (Box-folder 1: 11)
    - Stokes, Bernice, ca. 1942 (Box-folder 1: 11)
    - Roberts, Francine, ca. 1942 (Box-folder 1: 11)